bollyspice.com 2008-12-18

# Bollywood Spice - Privacy Policy

We do not collect any personal information from any of our members on our site. The forum may ask you for some, but you do not have to give details. We promise not to give or sell your personal information like your name or email address to anyone. 

This site is made only for our visitors’ enjoyment. We may use our forum members’ email addresses to contact them for important notices or news, but we mainly use our Private Messaging system built in our forums. Members will not receive any spam from us. If you happen to receive spam through PM from any of our members, please report them to an administrator. 

Visitors may want to subscribe to our newsletters, when we implement this feature in the future. This feature has not yet been decided to put on. 

We take no responsibility for any action or policies of any third parties who collect any information visitors may disclose on the forum, chat areas or other public areas on Bollywood Spice. If you have any quiries, please contact us using our contact forms found at the bottom of out homepage. We reserve the right to alter, modify or update this policy at any time. 

Bollywood Spice Forums are available to all our users. Any personal information provided within the forum area can be obtained by third parties. Please be careful while giving personal information in public places. Our forum staff deserves the right to remove any posts from the forum database at anytime without any warnings. 

BollySpice.com reserves the right to contact our members if abusive posting is found. Our forums is intended for all age groups under and over the age of 13. We recommend that parents/guardians of the young audience should regularly monitor the activity of their children on the internet at all times. 

We wish our visitors a pleasent time here at BollySpice. 

Faizan Qureshi   
Owner - BollySpice.com
